ROBERT ŠPAN

FRONT-END ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a frontend engineer with 3 years of experience.

At the moment I am mastering my skills in web development, my current victim being Angular.

I have a lot of experience with vanilla JavaScript, html and css as well as frameworks like React, Vue, Electron and Ionic.

CAREER EXPERTISE

- HTML5/CSS3/Sass
 Vanilla JS (ES5/ES6)
 Angular 8+ / TypeScript / RxJS
 React 16+ / Redux
 - Vue / VuexIonic / Electron

CONTACT DETAILS

Ljubljana, Slovenia +386 70 848 225 robi.span@gmail.com robispan.github.io github.com/robispan bitbucket.org/robispan linkedin.com/in/robert-špan

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Front-end Engineer

Geneplanet d.o.o., Mar 2020 - present

- Creating and managing web and hybrid apps in Angular / TypeScript
- Development of Angular libraries
- Writing unit / end-to-end tests

Stack: Angular 8+, TypeScript, Vanilla JS, RxJS, Sass, CI/CD Azure DevOps

Front-end Developer

I.R.V. d.o.o., Jan 2019 - Feb 2020

- Building web applications with Vue and React
- Building native frontend widgets for Content-Exchange websites
- Adapting frontend user experience (inserting targeted content into existing website structure, building custom widgets with targeted content)

Stack: ReactJS 16+, MobX, Vue/Vuex, Vanilla JS, Sass

Computer maintainance and Web Development

Hermes IPAL, Jun 2012 - Dec 2018

- Website maintenance (Joomla, Wordpress, WooCommerce)
- Computer software and hardware maintainance

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

edX.org (HarvardX)

CS50 - Introduction to computer science, 2018

- A broad and robust understanding of computer science and programming
- Concepts like abstraction, algorithms, data structures, encapsulation, resource management, security, software engineering, and web development
- Familiarity in a number of languages, including C, Python, SQL, and JavaScript plus CSS and HTML

SmartNinja.si

Web Development Course, 2018

- HTML and the basics of the web, CSS layouts, Git and GitHub, Bootstrap
- Basics of programming with Python, object-oriented programming (OOP)
- Data scraping, graphical user interface (GUI)
- Google App Engine, Jinja and GET requirements, POST, GAE models & Datastore
- Authentication and security, JSON & API

University of Ljubljana, Faculty of Arts

M.A in Psychology 2013